Aaron	Mosl	he [Dishv

Resume

Profile

Aaron Dishy is an archivist and information policy researcher based in Toronto, Canada. They hold a Bachelor of Arts in communications from McGill University (2016), and a Master of Information in critical information policy studies, and archives and records management, from the University of Toronto (2018). Aaron's work centers on new media policy, archives and records management, and the implementation of information and communication technologies. The preservation and accessibility of information ground their archival practice.

Education

Master of Information **Critical Information Policy Studies** Archives & Records University of Toronto (2016 - 2018)

Bachelor of Arts (with distinction) Communications Art History McGill University (2012 - 2016)

Bachelor of Arts Courses in Information Technology University of Copenhagen (2015)

Memberships

Association of Internet Researchers Association of Moving Image Archivists **Archives Association of Ontario**

Languages

English (Fluent) Hebrew/עברית (Fluent) French/Français (Reading)

Recommendations upon request.

Experience

Studio Archivist & Assistant

10.2018 — Present

Stephen Andrews & John Greyson Studio, Toronto

Acting as the studio archivist and assistant for artist Stephen Andrews and filmmaker John Greyson. This includes the production and maintenance of a functioning art archive including both analog and born-digital materials.

Research Fellow

09.2017 - 09.2018

University of Toronto, Toronto

Research fellow under Dr. Patrick Keilty. This research centered on analyzing and presenting data about online databases, social media studies, and contemporary archives.

Archives Assistant & Researcher Law Society of Ontario, Toronto

05 - 09.2017

Acted as a multi-media digitization assistant, developer of records retention schedules, manager of confidential information workflow, and legal researcher.

Digital Archivist

05 - 09.2016

Federation CJA, Montreal

Responsible for a community based exhibition, titled Juif d'Ici. Required archival knowledge, skill in digital curation, and understanding of preservation software.

Archives Intern

09.2015 - 06.2016

Centre for Oral History and Digital Storytelling, Montreal

Assisted in the digitization of the Montreal Life Stories Project, and upkeep of the COHDS Archive under archivist Kristen Young.

Preservation Intern

05.2015 - 01.2016

Canadian Jewish Archives, Montreal

Responsible for researching and digitizing new materials and exhibits throughout the Canadian Jewish Archives.

Research Fellow

05.2014 - 10.2015

Museum of Jewish Montreal, Montreal

Responsible for carrying out archival research about Montreal's Jewish Communities to expand the Museum's virtual exhibition database.

Skills

Volunteer

Archivist

Research and Publishing: academic & archival research, photoshop & layout design (Adobe Creative Suite) grant writing, copywriting, data visualization, collection, & analysis.

Digital Archivist Studio XX

2017-2019 Canadian Lesbian and Gay Archives

2015-2016

2015-2016

Archival: disk imaging techniques, metadata schema, digital forensics software, preservation software, standards (PREMIS) and

archival description software. Experience with XML and related technologies.

Layout Design Folio Magazine

www.aarondishy.net hello@aarondishy.net 1 (514) 266 6428 Toronto, Canada